40 Montcalm Drive, Kitchener N2B 2R1, Canada +1 548-333-7164

Dear Hiring Manager,

I am writing to show my interest in the position of web designer in your respective company. I am confident that I will be able to contribute to your web design team right away. I have a diverse set of skills that integrate innovative art and design ideas. In addition, my experience with Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, responsive websites, WordPress, ReactJs, and Node JS skills will enable me to play an important part in the implementation of your web design initiatives. The following are highlights of my skills and accomplishments:

- Creating and maintaining a website using HTML, CSS, and bootstrap and applying WCAG AA accessibility rules to deliveraccessible pages.
- Collaborate with UX designer to design pages using HTML5, CSS, and bootstrap.
- Review the site daily with a customer-first mindset, ensuring the integrity, consistency, and accuracy of product content. Maintain bugreports of the website on a daily basis.
- Update and improve the typography, colours, and layouts of Appreciated by my team leader for creating SVG animation explaining
- Human's financial needs that can easily be understood by the people who don't want to read more about the product, and It helps the company to get 3x the traffic of clients.

Enclosed is my resume for your review. I welcome the opportunity to discuss with you personally how my skills and strengths can best serve your company. I appreciate your time and consideration.

Sincerely, Vibhuti Gohil Sr. Web Designer



CONTACT ME



vibhutigohil77@gmail.com

+1 548-333-7164

https://vibhutigohil.myportfolio.com/work

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ vibhutigohil/

EDUCATION

Web Development
Conestoga College

2021 - 2022

Diploma in Web Designing Red & White Multimedia Education 2016 - 2017

Bachelors's in Computer Application

C. B. Patel Computer College

2011 - 2014

SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

HTML5

CSS

Bootstrap

Responsive Website

WordPress

React JS

Node JS

Vibhuti Gohil

Sr. Web Designer

PROFILE

I enjoy innovation and love to experiment with different ideas. My whole interest is related to Web Development. I enjoy coding, but I finally concluded that I am more creative and so my focus turned to web design.

4+ years of experience in responsive and accessible website design with HTML5, CSS3, Mongo, Express, Angular, React bootstrap plugins and Adobe Suits.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sr. Web Designer

2019 - 2021

NJ India Pvt. LTd. - Surat

- Creating and maintaining a website using HTML, CSS, and bootstrap and applying WCAG AA accessibility rules to deliveraccessible pages.
- Collaborate with UX designer to design pages using HTML5, CSS, and bootstrap.
- Review the site daily with a customer-first mindset, ensuring the integrity, consistency, and accuracy of product content. Maintain bugreports of the website on a daily basis.
- Update and improve the typography, colours, and layouts of Appreciated by my team leader for creating SVG animation explaining
- Human's financial needs that can easily be understood by the people who don't want to read more about the product, and It helps the company to get 3x the traffic of clients.

Web Designer

2017 - 2019

Skylink Business Automation LLP - Surat

- Major work here was creating Websites from scratch by using Adobe Products and coding them by using HTML5, CSS3 and Bootstrap library.
- Also managed website maintenance projects and repaired them with attractive designs.
- I also created a few websites in the WordPress framework. Most of the client Websites are from USA and UAE.
- Collaborating extensively with manager to better understand user experience solutions on search and benefits to projects.
- Update and improve the typography, colours, and layouts of websites.